Hello Hello Bhaiya as soon as this festival school
to my name is my name love and care for
ur from Darbhanga Bihar Mithila painting
in mid Lalit Narayan Mithila University
Darbhanga playlist music in mid of
probationary officer competition and challenges
hello hello bf mili
ab se vyakt hum number in all family mein
grand mother is the head of the family mein father is
arm and mother intact government teacher i have
two younger siblings he effectively is a
by-product of city on
267 Darbhanga Ishq cultural capital of Bihar
Darbhanga is also known as a hard of
Mithila Awaaz Darbhanga is also famous for
Mithila painting and Makhana language use tasveer language
and famous food a ritual for
android in the
world i want to join banking
sector at least one of the fastest
growing with student from our personality
and also like and subscribe our ACP mi ki
I serum means industrial credit and
investment  Corporation of India
ICICI Bank established in the floor
in wide dresses Mr. Sandeep Bakshi and
share Mr. Girish Chandra Das SBI Bank
branch in India phase available in India
is the first Indian to subscribe to
Loot hai
aise se bank online
a fan of yours and we are na bahut hi
effective hai
sir first of all I would like to thank
you for giving me this opportunity of
attachment and dedicated kar is faisal to
all my work and also I am a commerce
graduate bubs banking subscribe
my channel I will justify select kar li
next 9
ki thank you